The check in terminal at Brisbane International Terminal is all self service. If you require anything out of the norm or the self checkin doesn't work properly then there was only one person to help. There were at least 20 to 30 people waiting to check in bags with only 3 checkin booths operating. During the flight, the ability to buy a drink wasn't available until at least 2 hrs into the flight. The flight only goes for 3.5 hrs. Not enough vegetarian choices. Only chips, nuts etc. No vegetarian hot dish choices or sandwiches. This would not be my airline of choice in future. I may as well have flown Tiger Air, if I wanted this type of experience. Dreadful.

One flight attendant named Chris, he was delightful. The rest, an Asian woman and another older lady both bossy, and rude. Both really not happy to be there. Please change crew, that at least smile and act that they are loving their job. Horrendous service, was seating at the end of the plane, and simply the option of breakfast I wanted was not anymore. Not even a sorry I got. I didn’t have dinner cause they didn’t know the content of the ingredients of the food, in other airlines is written and they are aware. Neither I had breakfast, cause the option I could eat was not available. They are too old some of the crew and doesn’t look good. Bad presented and horrendous uniform, comparing with the Chilean crew that arrived at the same time go my god, what difference.

Once again seats chosen at time of booking had been resold and not available. Other seats with leg room were offered. Waste of $30 to choose seats.

Seats were behind a bulkhead and next to a toilet which was not available to us therefore I was expected to walk the length of cabin to 4 toilets shared by all economy passengers with a queue. I had a fractured toe!

Discovered on board service appalling.
Pay for anything other than water, poor tea or coffee,
Buy the right to view a movie $10, Not available to a couple traveling together as only one jack point.
Touch screen too sensitive to negotiate
A meat pie was available for $9 as was a toasted sandwich. All other snack food overpriced. 
I sat looking at what looked like vomit on the curtain dividing Premium Economy from Economy.
Total return price for two $1498 which included $60 for chosen seats which had been resold!
On collecting my bag discovered a smashed wheel! On reporting this problem we were told that the airline does not cover wheels or handles!Tthe absence of either of these renders a bag unusable. My husband carried it report the problem. The end result was successful with a replacement bag.
Staff although courtious, female staff look frumpy in Air NZ uniform which do not reflect who we are as New Zealanders. Purple with blobs of black represents what?
The fabric rides up the body as staff move about looking even more unglamourise.

No lumber support in the hard as hell seats and no room to adjustment the seat back. 
This is not the first disappointment with our airline. We travelled to Vancourver booking Premium Economy for greater long haul comfort to discover the seat appearing on the web page ony applied to planes on other routes. 
Avoid Air NZ if you can.

We booked the dream trip of a life time, or so we thought, along with business class tickets for a once in a lifetime trip and it turned into a nightmare thanks to Air New Zealand! Seats were confirmed by email 6 months before the flight. For whatever reason, the seats were removed from our itinerary 4 days before the flight -- ok, so I called Air New Zealand who was (SUPPOSEDLY) working on trying to get our original seating back. By the evening before the flight, the original seat were not available, so I chose 2 other seats and printed out the boarding passes. We were one of the first in line to board, but the boarding passes scanned incorrect seating. We were told to sit in the seats behind the ladies scanning the passes until almost all the passengers were boarded. Then we were given seats by the restroom, which we had been told were among the worst seats on the plane. Will NEVER fly Air New Zealand again! Bought and paid for first class tickets and were treated like criminals for no reason!

Service was crap on the airplane.I picked up trash under my seat and I waited for air steward I tried to give it to him and he stared at me and he stared at trash and stared me again than his face changed.He looked at me like I was a piece of poo.

Having seen New Zealand Airlines as part of world's top 10 I am prompted to write this review. I am 6'2' and I have never been so cramped on any flight before or since. The plane was old and I was jammed in a seat next to an elderly lady in the aisle seat so was not able to move for the whole flight. I suffered neck pain which resulted in medical treatment which curtailed and essentially spoiled our trip to New Zealand. Will never fly Air New Zealand long haul again. Have said all that we did one domestic flight which was excellent and we lived the country and the people. This happened October 2015 as I stated earlier my reason for this review is shock at NZA being rated so highly.

The seats are cramped. The food is awful. You have to beg for water and the flight attendants are lackluster. A most unpleasant 12 hours in the air. I will never fly this airline again.

we flew to auckland january 2016. we have NEVER been so uncomfortable on a flight!!! the seats were so narrow and there was poor leg room. during meals, i had my elbows pinned to my sides and yet my husband still complained that i was encroaching on his space. there was no way to avoid it with these terrible seats! and this was a very long flight--something like 12 or 13 hours. NEVER AGAIN!!! we strongly recommend AVOIDING air new zealand.


I travel in business class for comfort, I am a rather large male and I need the extra room business class normally provides. As a non-drinker all the offers of fine wine and other drinks are of no interest to me. Returning from a holiday in the Cook islands I was looking forward to flying on the Boing Dreamliner (787-9) that Air New Zealand had recently starting using on the Sydney - Rarotonga Route - how wrong I was. 
The layout of the business class cabin is 3 abreast, one seat against each sides and one in the middle, but the seats do not face forward but are at an angle, the back of your head is against the window. The "A" seats on the left side face the back of the middle row, the middle row and the row of seats on the right face each other, you cannot escape from constantly looking at your fellow passengers across the aisle, no privacy whatsoever.

The seats at 22" width are pretty standard business class seat width, but because they are at an angle and to separate you from the passenger in front or behind there are walls on either side up to shoulder height for most people - so the seat is 22" wide from bum to shoulder. Once you are in the seat you cannot move your arms, it was like being in a straight jacket. It's difficult to eat as you cannot move your elbows. The seats convert to a flat bed but that is no more comfortable as it's almost impossible to lie on your back, with your head in a dark box - you wouldn't want to be claustrophobic.

The staff are great and the food - what I could eat was not too bad but it cannot make up for the hours of total discomfort. What is funny (sort of) Air New Zealand use some of their rugby players in their advertisements and in-flight films. I cannot imagine that most of them would fit or be comfortable in those seats.

An absolutely horrendous flight, AIR NEW ZEALAND - never again !!!


Absolutely terrible customer service on this flight. I travelled home from Canada with 6 freshly broken ribs and an ingrown toenail. At check in the weighing machine said I was 10 kg over and I insisted on re-weighing as that couldn't be correct, the customer service assistant refused at first but then re-weighed, once she did this it turns out I was half a kilo over the limit and she said I needed to re-pack, I told her I was in pain due to my ribs and it would be hard to do, she said that's my problem and to hurry up and re-pack, one of the most distressing painful situations I have ever found myself in. 

On board the flight the once dinner had been served and the lights were low I was on my way to the bathroom, and due to my ingrown toenail I was wearing thongs, one of my toes hit something sharp a started bleeding profusely. All the air hosts were scuffling about and I asked for help but they seemed to ignore me until I showed them the blood pouring out of my toe. They didn't say anything they just gave me a band-aid, I sat down on a seat closest to me to put the band-aid on and one of the staff said to "MOVE IMMEDIATELY FROM MY SEAT" I said I'm just putting on a band-aid on my bleeding toe but she said it doesn't matter, I'm sitting in an "off-limits seat" so I had to stand and try and put on the band-aid. 

Absolutely disgusting display of empathy and customer service. I will never fly Air New Zealand again.


We were travelling from Heathrow to Auckland on the 21st January. We had booked the complete flight through Singapore Airlines but ANZ were the airline from Singapore as a code share. We were on a 787 Dreamliner so I assumed that our seats would be as good as on the A380 with Singapore Airlines. I had also heard good things about ANZ as an airline so we were not expecting any problems. Wrong on both counts! 
The seats were cramped and very uncomfortable and the service left a lot to be desired. On top of this our luggage was left behind in Singapore! 

I don't expect a fantastic experience when flying economy but the level of service that we received left an awful lot to be desired. I could not help but make comparisons with Singapore airlines and they fell well short in every respect. The meals were 'ok' but they seemed reluctant to offer any drinks other than water or orange juice. On a long flight I would expect to be offered alcohol three or four times, as we were with Singapore. With ANZ this was only done during the dinner service. I realised late in the flight that drinks could be ordered through the seat back touch screen. It was a shame that this was not told to us!

Before leaving the UK I had asked Singapore airlines about the short amount of time between arriving and leaving Changi Airport (less than 1 hour) I was told that this would not be a problem as the aircraft would be very close to each other. When we got off the A380 we found that the ANZ aircraft was at the opposite end of the very long terminal building! Several of us who were on the same flight had to practically run to the departure gate to catch the flight. We then arrived in Auckland and went to collect out luggage, or at least attempt to! Surprise, surprise, it had been left in Singapore! The customer service guy for ANZ told us that there had not been enough time to transfer the bags between the flights! He told us to return the next day at 12:00 and collect our bags. We were given a survival pack of toiletries & a tee shirt and sent on our way. We returned the next day at 12 and were then told that the bags would be another two and a half hours....not impressed. We then returned and waited another half an hour for our bags. The lady behind the counter then treated us to a lecture about labelling our cases correctly!

After all of this the first day of our holiday had been a complete waste of time. I contacted Singapore Airlines to complain and they told me that the last carrier of the journey was responsible for any luggage problems. 

I then sent an email to ANZ who told me that it was my own fault for booking the flights so closely together! I pointed out that the booking had been made through Singapore Airlines directly and they then told me that if I submitted receipts for any out of pocket expenses I would be reimbursed. I replied that I had not had any out of pocket expenses as we were intending to stay in Auckland for our first day. What we had lost was the first day of our very expensive holiday as we were stuck at the airport for most of it. 

Air New Zealand just ignored this comment.

I don't expect a grovelling apology for this sort of thing but to be dismissed out of hand was inexcusable. Some gesture of good will such as a small refund, or an upgrade would have sufficed. Now I will share my poor experience with my friends and word will get round. Poor service on a long haul trip is the last thing that you need. 

Needless to say I will never fly with this airline again

Our flight was initially delayed, then cancelled, we were not told anything about new flights, when i called up air NZ reservations to book onto a virgin flight to Christchurch. i was told they were confirmed. however when we went to check in, Air NZ hadn't ticketed out seats. It took them an hour to assist, then this flight was delayed, ended up landing in CHCH at 1.30am to be told they had no idea we were coming and air NZ had NOT organised accommodation. The next morning flight was cancelled, ended up calling reservations again to get on the 10.00am flight from CHCH to Qtwn and finally arrived at the destination 24 hours after we were supposed to. THEN, when going through the hassle of getting to queenstown, Air NZ had CANCELLED our return flight the next day. So when we went to check in, we did not have a seat..... Very poorly organised.


Traveling solo with an infant, where the seat is next to "business class" toilet. I was not allowed to use the toilet even when the toilet was free, and was asked to walk to the end of the aircraft to use "economy class" toilet with my 7 month old baby. Absolutely pathetic in understanding the needs of infants and thereby providing a terrible customer experience. Not once was i checked on to see how we were going.(All good airlines do!) Of course, as they seemed to be more interested in providing an experience for their business class passengers.None of my business how they treat other classed passengers but horrible experience for us, especially with the infant. Had it not been for the elderly lady who was sitting next to me, it would have been one extremely hard journey. Will not travel again with them with children, already have nightmares of my return travel with this airline, Unfortunate, that being a kiwi(known for their care for others) airline, it is so cold to the needs of their own passengers


According to Trip Advisor I have over 60,000 readers of my of my past reviews. I hope you all read this one and act accordingly.
I am a 70 year old Canadian male and I am a retired Toronto Police Sergeant that served my City of Toronto for 37 years. I did it all on the streets of Toronto. I am also a Veteran of the Canadian Armed Forces prior to becoming a Police Officer. I am passionately proud of serving my Country and my City. I am fortunate enough to have a CF! Veterans card from the Canadian Forces Morale and Welfare Services which which allows me to travel with 3 check pieces of luggage at 75 pounds per bag as opposed to the normal 2 pieces of luggage at 50 pounds per bag. This CF1 card is honoured by, Air Canada, Delta Airlines, West Jet, to name a few. For the past number of years my wife and I have traveled extensively to Europe, the Caribbean, and recently, the Pacific region (Hawaii, Australia and Bali).
On the 19th of January 2017, we embarked on a 5 week journey to Hawaii, Australia and Bali Indonesia.
Given the fact I had the CF1 Veterans Card, we packed 2 pieces of checked baggage that were knowingly each 61 pounds. Ironically the 21 pounds over the normal 50 pounds per baggage were gifts for our relatives in Australia.
We flew out of Toronto on Delta Airlines operated by West Jet Airlines (star alliance).
to Vancouver and then to Oahu Hawaii, Delta Airlines and West Jet honoured my CF1 Veterans Card and there was no problem with the 21 pounds over 50 pounds.
We stayed in Oahu Hawaii for 5 days, and left for Australia on the 24th of January 2017 at 6.30am on Air New Zealand flight # NZ0009.
At 6.30am we checked our luggage in with the Air New Zealand employee at the check in counter and we were told we were 21 pounds over weight. 
I told the check in clerk, yes I know that, but I am exempt from that 50 pound per checked in piece of luggage with my Canadian Forces Veterans CF1 Card and presented it to her. 
The clerk checked her computer and told me that Air New Zealand does NOT Honour that card or any Active Military or Veterans Cards traveling on Air New Zealand Airlines. This disgusted me and I asked to speak to a Supervisor. The Supervisor repeated what the check in clerk told me with complete indifference.
I was forced to pay $300.00 U.S. Dollars for the over weight 21 pounds of checked in baggage. I had no choice to do it, so I paid it. BUT after they had my $300 USD cash and my luggage was gone on the conveyor belt, the Supervisor told me in a matter of fact tone as she walked away, that if I had brought a third piece of luggage, the penalty for the 3rd piece of luggage would have been much less then the $300.00 USD I just paid her. 
I wasn't going to let this ignorance destroy our trip, but in my mind I vowed I would file a complaint with Air New Zealand when I got back to Canada. AND I DID exactly that.
back in Canada,
I filed a detailed complaint with Air New Zealand and they immediately agreed to refund me $205.00 USD of my $300 USD I paid them in Oahu, but it was not based on the CF1 card I was traveling with, the refund was based on what the Supervisor for Air New Zealand told me at the airport in Hawaii about having the 3rd bag and it would have cost me much less then the $300.00. Air New Zealand went on to tell me that I would have to pay the 3rd bag fee of $95.00 USD, which I agreed to because again, I had no choice. I was just trying to recover the lost money I paid them.
In a separate email, I questioned Air New Zealand's corporate policy about the treatment of Active Military and Veterans traveling on their airlines and they refused to comment other then to say they treat all passengers egual. 

All of our freedoms are based on the ultimate sacrifice, millions of soldiers have freely given to us and Air New Zealand does not care about that. 

When I travel through US airports, the vast majority of them have a free, private lounge for active Military personnel and Veterans to relax in while waiting for their connecting flights 

Given the temperament of the world today, I personally find that Air New Zealand's attitude is not only disappointing, it's disgusting.

For what it is worth I hope Trip Advisor appreciates this review and publishes this it.

This was a code-share flight for United. Flight number NZ6. You have to be a child to be comfortable in economy class on Air New Zealand's Boeing 777-300. Small seat size is exacerbated by poor placement of seat-to-floor supports which do not clearly define under-seat storage space so there is "bleed over" from your neighbor. Further, starboard center aisle seat gives up foot space to the electronics module. Overhead storage bins the smallest I have seen on aircraft used for long-haul flights. Dinner meal was adequate but scrambled eggs at breakfast was the worst food I have ever tasted. Won't be on Air NZ again if I can help it.

I was on a Virgin Australia ticket and Air NZ operated the flight. As a platinum frequent flyer i was able to use the "premium" check in area - think kiosks in a room rather than open in the terminal -you do everything while a staff member watches you. Got allocated bad seating - apparently they have to look after their own frequent flyers first and that doesn't include VA FF. Air NZ lounge in Auckland is new but already showing age from cheap construction. Entry to male toilet door was not shutting properly, The self service drinks area is badly organised, one choice of milk (skim/trim) and no staff around for assistance. Food had run out. Barista coffee was OK. No magazines or newspapers and I think they are using dial-up internet so I used roaming on my phone which was faster. Air NZ have managed to de-humanize the experience of flying, its scan and help yourself - so long as someone has remembered to bring the food out and do some maintenance. I would suggest using Emirates/QANTAS as better options across the Tasman, certainly the lounges of both are superior. Flight was on 777 - OK interior, old style video and the food was small portions and uninspiring. Meal tray had coffee stains on so not cleaned. Everything seemed to be the minimum they could get away with.

Air New Zealand management should be called the Flip Flop Department. They say 'seating allocations cannot change after a boarding pass has been printed except for load balancing or safety requirements'

Well when I boarded (and was first to board) with boarding pass for seat 3C I had a Goldie Locks sitting in my chair', some how she had managed to sneak onto the plane prior to boarding and the crew had let her 'sit in my chair and was still there' unlike to storey where Goldie Locks fled the 3 Bears House, she informed me that the crew had snuck her on prior to boarding and said it was OK to sit in my chair, luckey the crew had the magic marker pen to change my allocated seat to 5D, now I'm not sure how that comprised Civil Aviation Authority safety and security requirements but I guess that the magic marker pen wasn't integrated to the rest of the compliance network.

When asked to respond neither Air NZ's CEO or Loyalty Manager responded, I figured that they were busy writing up new fairy tales for their customers, who knows????

Terrible ground service, ripped us off for extra luggage costs $400 to transport 2 small bags from ChCh to Perth (competitors like Quantas great airline charge $25-$40 per bag. Flight was pretty average too. ChCh ground staff were unhelpful despite our itinerary showing we paid a near full fare and no mention of no bags included and for some reason did not have bags included on one return leg. We were bluntly told leave your bags behind or pay $400. Ok anyone can make a mistake but we got almost no response when we complained and just blunt without any explanation terse rejection of our complaint. No phone call nothing - they just suck - We will never fly Air NZ again anywhere they have no values, no customer service - just terrible.

had another bad travel,had problems again getting up and down steps,did have wheelchair assistance and once again trouble getting in and out of toilet,very uncomfortable,shaky plane ,not good at all


Worst baggage policy ever for international flight. Our baggage allowance was 23Kgs + 7Kgs (Carry on) and our main bag was only 14Kgs and second bag 8Kgs ( NO Carry on baggage) . As per check-in staff only one piece was allowed, even if the weigh was way less than the allowed limit. I will need to speak to his supervisor to make an exception to check-in both.

I was made to wait while he waited for the supervisor and after a while walked me to the Supervisor ( the staff did not bother much about our situation) . The Supervisor arrives and was sticking to the company's fine prints ( Terms & Conditoin) which always covers their back. Even after explained the situation that I need wheel chair assistance and cannot carry weigh hence the 2 bags need to be checkd-in, but still he kept on insisting about the fine prints. He was very unfriendly and was in a defencive mode, than trying to understand his customers situation and help or at least empathise.


We upgraded our seats to premium economy to get more leg room. I do not think there was any difference in leg room, i thought we had less leg space than jet star or virgin Australia in economy. We were only offered water, tea, or coffee. At least on the worst American airlines we get soda and a small bag of pretzels. Very disappointed with poor cabin service.

Air New Zealand put on an extra flight in January that they were unable to service. This caused a delay of 18 hours for our travel plans.
Placed on another airline, stuck in a row of three seats. (Was booked on premium economy with a row of two seats)Had to climb over people to go to bathroom. Food choices not transferred unable to eat on plane. Horrible flight. 
Missed connecting flights and lost hotel booking. Missed shows we were booked for.
Not able to claim back on insurance as insurance company claims air nz incompetence.
Air NZ poor communicators, rude and uncaring.
Waste of money.

Our plane was orginally delayed for 40 mins in Christchurch, we were loaded on board with a promise to depart. However due to a technical issue we could not depart. They closed off the AC ( it was about 29 outside) promising that the issue would be fixed in 10 mins..... 80 mins later we left, no saftey briefing 

I was imbrassed to say that this is our national air line


Was excited to fly back to NZ after a most awesome week away in Asia. Just prior to leaving NZ, I received a new Airpoints card from Air New Zealand labelled 'Elite' which made me feel a bit special as I had flown a few times over the last year and the last card I had was that teal coloured card that all New Zealanders got recently. The card came with some information about using the Koru lounges but as my next flight was from Singapore, there were no Koru lounges there so free lounge access in Singapore was not possible. The check in lady offered a paid lounge, something called SATS lounge but the cost was prohibitive, :( but Changi is an awesome place and there were millions of places to grab preflight meals etc so did not feel bad by not using this SATS lounge and paying $50 for a simple meal.
At the gate, the boarding officer was quite rude but put this down to being a one off experience. I was among the last to board, I sneakily tried to be one of the first to get on the plane but they were very strict about letting passengers with "status" board prior and insisted I wait until I was called. I was hoping that this "Airpoints Elite" card they gave me might be helpful here but the boarding officer recognised me from prior and refused to let me approach the podium so never got the chance to see if this elite card would assist, but can only infer that Air NZ "elite status" benefits do not extend to prioritised boarding but that was not a huge deal as there was a queue on the gangway to board the plane.
I arrived at my seat to find someone else in it and when I asked the staff, they told me that I had the choice to either move to this person's originally assigned seat or find alternative arrangements to get home - ie another flight. No explanation was given as to why another person was in my seat and why I had to move to a middle seat in the last row directly in front of the toilets. The entertainment system in my seat was not working at all and the staff mentioned that "technical difficulties" prevented me from assisting me so the entire flight was without in-flight entertainment. Being in the last row, they ran out of meals due to a "catering situation" and I was starving until the last hour and a half when they offered the inflight dinner.
Whilst I don't know what this "Airpoints elite" membership entails is in any great detail, the service received was atrocious and I will never use this airline again. A work colleague suggested that Airpoints elite status was poorly regarded by Air NZ and that they were more attentive to their Koru members, which I understand, but don't see the reason in spending close to $800 a year as I only fly every now and then


Just spent 3 hours trying to contact Air NZ in Australia. Uncontactable. State of the art planes, avionics etc, but can't answer phones. Perhaps they are "closed" as a 9 - 5 business would be? If they are, then programme the phone system to say so .Can't fault the warm fuzzies they create with the clever marketing, cool paint jobs. How hard should it be to contact them? Harder than MH370? Unacceptable from a first world airline.


Never put fragile items in checked bag, as ANZ did not deny dropping my bag and destroying my laptop, but claimed in the ticket terms and conditions, that I could carry on "small portable devices" as an extra piece, even though my 17inch laptop is hardly "small". I was just over the 7 kilos hand luggage limit and had to put my laptop in my checked bag with clothing around it. I have never done this before, but I was flying on an hour long flight on a prop plane so thought it would be ok. I was not offered a fragile label which I doubt would have helped anyway. Before boarding I watched my bag go flying out of cargo door and landing hard on the runway. A baggage handler was catching other bags but mine was the one that hit the deck. I asked the ground crew before boarding and was told that they had to repack the luggage so some luggage comes off the plane and then repacked. On arrival I checked the laptop but it was when I tried to charge it the cord would not go into its slot so the computer would not charge. On my return flight the next day I took it to the lost/damaged baggage counter in Christchurch airport which handled both domestic and international flights. It took a long time with many tired travellers and finally when I was seen the man behind the desk insisted on trying to push the charge cord very hard into the computer which of course made no difference. I was given a form and at the end he told me to take it to my personal insurance. I was shocked as surely this damage is directly due to ANZ negligence. On arrival back to Dunedin I spoke to ANZ again and they pointed out the new camera system that shows the public the bags being put on the baggage carousels by the baggage handlers. How ironic, obviously resulting from previous baggage damages. And after repeated calls, I was told that I could have taken my computer on board as an extra piece as a "small portable device" which I and the check in lady did not recognise a 17 inch laptop being "small" but I was reassured on the phone that I should and could have hand carried it as an extra piece to my 7kg hand luggage. Air New Zealand refused to accept any liability for their destroying my computer. It was a write off as the motherboard was damaged. Shame on you Air New Zealand. I have been a faithful frequent flyer for years but this incident has made me rethink about my future airline carrier options.

We were extremely well served by the aircrew on our flights in both directions. However, the touchdown we had to make for refuelling at Los Angeles airport was simply awful. We were looking forward to a two hour stopover thinking we could do some shopping, take in some food and drink and generally chill out a bit. The reality was we were shunted from one end of the airport to the other to join a single queue of literally thousands of people having to be processed through US immigration. It took 1 hour 40 minutes to do this! Then we had to hastily dash back to the same place we'd started from to get back on board. We already had ESTAs so I just don't get why we had to be put through all of this, I was in transit? My fingerprints and iris patterns are now on record somewhere without my consent, I feel quite outraged by this. To make things worse we had to endure exactly the same thing on the route back home. NEVER AGAIN will I travel in that direction. Air New Zealand needs to negotiate and set up a lounge just off the boarding/descent point to prevent passengers having to undergo this horrible experience. Nobody should go through this after a 12 hour or so flight.


Just spent 1.5 hour at the ticketing counter in aline of 12 people.glacier s are moving way faster.
flight was as mediocre as they come. Food and drinks are reasonable, but nothing special at all, service.... they are so tired and slow. what service?
sheer dissapointment


NEVER fly Air NZ if you have kids, especially unaccompanied kids flights. Their online portal is faulty, their customer service woeful, they couldn't care less and then the final indignity- they charge me!!!

A massive customer service fail! Suggest flying Emirates or Qantas 

Oh, I'm a co-owner of a travel agency, guess what airline I'll recommend sidestepping..?


Staff on the ground rude and intolerant. I was seven months pregnant when I took this flight and the staff at both airports were absolutely the rudest, most miserable people I have ever met aside from a couple of nice men. One lady forced me to lift my heavy suitcase up onto the scales even though I was aware how much it weighed and she saw me earlier weighing it and taking things out to correct the weight. I told her this but she still made me lift it again onto the scales on my own just to say "oh I thought it would be over the weight limit". 

Check in was absolute chaos and I needed to speak with the lady manning it about a certain American visa that was needed which I hadn't known about. Because of the chaos I wasn't able to talk to her until it became an absolute emergency and when it finally became possible she shouted at me "why the hell didn't you come and see me earlier!" Despite this she didn't attempt to help me and just sent me "over there, she'll deal with you." 

The third woman I had the pleasure of dealing with (behind the desk this time) was no better, just as rude and long story short I ended up in floods of tears in the middle of the airport having to pay for another flight (to london). 

I am not saying there were no errors on my part during this whole fiasco but a little understanding, help and politeness would be appreciated having coughed up £2000. They were appalling and I wish I knew their names.

The on flight staff, however, were fantastic and I wish I knew their names also.


In my last 15 years of international air travel Air NewZealand is the worst and I think it is so bad nothing else can beat it in the future either. 

Following are the reasons why:
(1) The seats on international flight are narrower than domestic flights in USA

(2) The leg room is barely enough for a 5'10" tall guy like me to not knee the seat in the front

(3) There is no individual air for each seat. So, imagine sitting in a tight airplane with 2 other humans and you are snorkeling each others breath and no fresh air. 

(4) After eating their dinner and breakfast you actually appreciate McDonalds 

(5) They allow only 1 checked bag with max 50 pounds for international flight. This is the first as I have used Lufthansa, Quantas, Air India, Emirates, etc. etc. and never have I gotten only 1 checked bag allowance for international flight

(6) You are allowed 1 carry on with 15 pound weight limit. Even if your bag fits the dimensions, make sure it is under weight as they will randomly police the weight of carry-on also. They will force you to pay more after policing your bags. 

(7) Toilets are nasty as if like next passenger is supposed to clean it if someone from previous night left it dirty.

(8) The air flow is such that the plane gets hots and when you find yourself suffocating and on point of choking in hot humid human breath, plane AC turns on. That is when you take a deep breath. The AC then stops working. I asked one crew member why it was like that and they said, for long distance flights they want to save on fuel. 

I have never spent a night in coffin but you don't need to either, just take an Air NewZealand international flight and you will get real life experience of being in a coffin.

